<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- edited with XMLSPY v2004 rel. 2 U (http://www.xmlspy.com) by Ed Beach (Firaxis Games) -->
<GameData>
	<LocalizedText>
		<!--CIVILIZATION-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_PTH_HATTENGAARD_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hattengaard</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_PTH_HATTENGAARD_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hattengaard</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_PTH_HATTENGAARD_ADJECTIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hattengaardian</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CIVILIZATION_PTH_HATTENGAARD_DESCRIPTION_PTH_CIVILIZATION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hattengaard</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Pedia-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_CIVINFO_PTH_HATTENGAARD_LOCATION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Europe</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CIVINFO_PTH_HATTENGAARD_POPULATION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>We're too drunk to take a census.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CIVINFO_PTH_HATTENGAARD_SIZE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Well that depends. How many vodka bottles are in a kilometer?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CIVINFO_PTH_HATTENGAARD_CAPITAL" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hattengaard</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_PTH_HATTENGAARD_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Top Hats Exposed: Part 1</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_PTH_HATTENGAARD_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Top Hats Exposed: Part 2</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_PTH_HATTENGAARD_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Top Hats Exposed: Part 3</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_PTH_HATTENGAARD_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Top Hats Exposed: Part 4</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_PTH_HATTENGAARD_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Top Hats Exposed: Part 5</Text>
		</Row>
		
		
		<!--Cities-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PTH_HATTENGAARD_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hattengaard</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PTH_HATTENGAARD_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Melrakkanes</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PTH_HATTENGAARD_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Kollshamarr</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PTH_HATTENGAARD_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Deildara </Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PTH_HATTENGAARD_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Brynjudalr</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PTH_HATTENGAARD_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Skorraholt</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PTH_HATTENGAARD_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Lysa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PTH_HATTENGAARD_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hakonarhella</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PTH_HATTENGAARD_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ladytopjod</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PTH_HATTENGAARD_10" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Brattahlio</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PTH_HATTENGAARD_11" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Bramsloekr</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PTH_HATTENGAARD_12" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hvalsey</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PTH_HATTENGAARD_13" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Lofot</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PTH_HATTENGAARD_14" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Kvia</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PTH_HATTENGAARD_15" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hatropolis</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PTH_HATTENGAARD_16" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Oddsass</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PTH_HATTENGAARD_17" Language="en_US">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PTH_HATTENGAARD_18" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Lonlond</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PTH_HATTENGAARD_19" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Berserkseyrr</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PTH_HATTENGAARD_20" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Landeyjar</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PTH_HATTENGAARD_21" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Skagi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PTH_HATTENGAARD_22" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Grjota</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PTH_HATTENGAARD_23" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Fjoll</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PTH_HATTENGAARD_24" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Kolbeinsstaoir</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PTH_HATTENGAARD_25" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Skalmarnes</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PTH_HATTENGAARD_26" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Alfsoss</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PTH_HATTENGAARD_27" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hofsfell</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PTH_HATTENGAARD_28" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Gaular</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PTH_HATTENGAARD_29" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Akranes</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_PTH_HATTENGAARD_30" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Gil</Text>
		</Row>
		
		
		
		<!--Citizens-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_MALE_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Potato Pole</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_MALE_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Past THaC</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_MALE_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Drunken7Dragoon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_MALE_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sith Lord THaC</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_MALE_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>SpaceCouncil</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_MALE_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>James R. Basterd</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_MALE_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hammer</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_MALE_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Chris4197</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_MALE_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>JonathanExley</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_MODERN_MALE_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>PotatoHollow</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_MODERN_MALE_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>PartTim3Hobo</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_MODERN_MALE_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Dugachug</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_MODERN_MALE_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>OppressorFessor</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_MODERN_MALE_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Finntrovert</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_MODERN_MALE_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>WalkerTrips</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_MODERN_MALE_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>oiscream</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_MODERN_MALE_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>LiquidEvilGaming</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_MODERN_MALE_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ledger Balance</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_MODERN_MALE_10" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Nonthiest Yeast</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_FEMALE_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>LadyTopHat</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_FEMALE_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>shanarith</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_FEMALE_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>RoseLawliet</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_FEMALE_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Meranima</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_FEMALE_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>TheCinemaNurse</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_FEMALE_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Missye042</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_FEMALE_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>CuteGamerGrill</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_FEMALE_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Chantel</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_FEMALE_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Jynxed</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_FEMALE_10" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Lara</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_MODERN_FEMALE_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ashantha</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_MODERN_FEMALE_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ladysharp</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_MODERN_FEMALE_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>logicsharpener</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_MODERN_FEMALE_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>BarBot</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_MODERN_FEMALE_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>jonathan's sister</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_MODERN_FEMALE_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>D3moira</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_MODERN_FEMALE_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>helenx_Lutja</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_MODERN_FEMALE_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Spanish Inn Physician</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_MODERN_FEMALE_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Vandipitty</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_PTH_HATTENGAARD_MODERN_FEMALE_10" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Console Fairy</Text>
		</Row>
		
		
		
		<!--LEADER-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_LEADER_PTH_THAC_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Top Hats And Champagne</Text>
		</Row>

		
		<!--DOM-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_PTH_THAC" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Well looks like you've survived another alcoholic poisoning. Hello, my name is Top Hats and Champagne. Welcome to Hattengaard where we're ruled by drunks and vikings alike.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		
		<!--Civilopedia-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_PTH_THAC_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Top Hats and Champagne</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_PTH_THAC_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Plunderer of Alcohol</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_PTH_THAC_QUOTE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Don't let a trip to the emergency room stop your love for alcohol. - September 4th, 2017</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_PTH_THAC_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>
				Top Hats and Champagne was born in the remote Siberian wilderness. He was raised by a family of wolves. He learned to live off the land until he was 15.
				He was eventually recruited to serve in the Hitler Youth at a young age when Germany invaded Russia in World War 2.
				After the war he went into hiding and managed to join Al Qaeda.
				He was then exiled to the dropbear infested land known as Australia. He started a YouTube channel and Twitch channel in hopes of raising money to one day return to Germany to make Hitler proud.
				He plans on forcing his Twitch subscribers into a concentration camp to work on potato fields for 16 hours a day. He plans on holding PartTim3Hobo in a cage and forcing me to make weekly highlights for him until he died.
				Meanwhile all of PartTim3Hobo's hopes and dreams will be burned in a fire. On his Twitch streams he regularly mocks his viewers.
				He also wields his mods like a powerful oppressive shitlord and times out anyone who falls out of line. He has even revealed on stream multiple times just how much of a degenerate he really is.
				His wife is also in on the act. Lady Top Hat is secretly preparing a rocket that she is building using Top Hats' Patreon money.
				It will detonate in London in an attempt to kill all the people who supported Brexit.
				We cannot allow this to happen. PartTim3Hobo even attempted to send an undercover agent to raid his treasury but he was caught in the act.
				We must unite as one between both Team Chaos and Team Ordah. We must also get more developers on our side. We must fight back!
				Or in the words of General The Destroyer "Now it's war. Now it's fucking, fucking war!
				Shortly after seeing Top Hats get the better hand of several of my generals PartTim3Hobo ran to the CIA to see if they could build him a weapon that could defeat Top Hats and Champagne once and for all.
				The CIA agreed to start building a secret project titled Project Dugachug.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_PTH_THAC_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>
				The campaign suffered a setback. During the 24 hour stream Top Hats made a secret phone call to Twitch and had PartTim3Hobo timed out for spewing propaganda.
				Fortunately he was able to work around this by changing his IP address and resuming my propoganda work.
				This timeout also managed to incite many members into laughter. We could only hope that this raises their morale.
				So this is all well and good but PartTim3Hobo discovered a new secret.
				One that may change the outcome of this fight.
				PartTim3Hobo implanted a camera into Lara's eye.
				The footage he recovered from her had revealed something about Top Hats and Champagne that he never knew before.
				Top Hats has managed to invent a cloning machine.
				He has used this cloning machine to create more copies of himself.
				He is tried to hide a few of these copies of himself by giving them different nationalities.
				But PartTim3Hobo managed to hack into his webcam to see exactly what these clones look like.
				However the cloning technology hasn't been perfected.
				And let's just say that some of the clones came out...retarded.
				Seeing as how Top Hats and Champagne had invented his own cloning technology PartTim3Hobo figured he needed to develop his own cloning method.
				However he decided not to clone himself.
				So who did he clone?
				He cloned the nightwalker, who glides through oceans of blood, someone who is beyond human, a monster who's power radiates through the darkness,
				and cast's a shadow on darkness itself.
				His name is Hammer. But the best part is, he made his clone German.
				But before everyone went and started singing the Hell March theme there was one problem.
				Remember how it said Top Hats' cloning technique wasn't perfected yet?
				Well neither was ours so our German Hammer clone didn't quite work out.
				He's roughly what Hammer is but with one major exception.
				In his desire to expose Top Hats for the man he truly is PartTim3Hobo needed to strike fear into his entire chain of command.
				He needed someone who can trigger Top Hats with just the sound of his voice.
				He needed the man who has at one point unleashed a special kind of hell upon Top Hats.
				This means that he had to turn to someone who has known Top Hats and Champagne for a fairly long time.
				His name was BulletBarry.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_PTH_THAC_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>
				In Hobo's quest to expose Top Hats and Champagne for the man he truly is, PartTim3Hobo recieved some devastating news.
				Remember the rocket I told you about back in the first chapter?
				Well sadly Lady Top Hat has managed to finish the rocket, launch it, and wipe out nearly all of London.
				Fearing the consequences of their actions Top Hats and Champagne and Lady Top Hat flee into space.
				They had been preparing for this day for a long time.
				A call is sent out for all available space fighters in the area to respond.
				Much to Hobo's delight, there was an overwhelming response.
				However news of Top Hats fleeing into space was not only recieved by the Top Hatters.
				There's an old saying that the enemy of my enemy is my friend.
				Well as it turns out there was a much greater threat than we had anticipated.
				This forced the Top Hatters to fight together for the greater good of themselves.
				His name was GeneralTheDestroyer.
				In the unfolding chaos of the battle he was stealthily taken prisoner by Top Hats and Champagne.
				He brought me back to Earth and relegated me to his basement.
				He didn't know what he had planned for him.
				He knew he had to find a way to escape.
				You know, there's an old saying out there.
				The enemy of my enemy is my friend.
				But very often people leave out the last part of that sentence.
				The enemy of my enemy is my friend, until he becomes my enemy again.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_PTH_THAC_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>
				And now PartTim3Hobo is in the basement of Top Hats and Champagne's house.
				He rummaged through his old stuff and found a really old laptop which I'm using to make this video.
				He wants you all to know that no matter how dire of a situation he may be in, he is always committed to exposing the truth about Top Hats and Champagne.
				Anyways, once he managed to get his old computer up and running the first thing he did was check his email.
				He was pleasantly surprised to see that he recieved an email from the CIA with great news.
				Project Dugachug was a success.
				However rumors of Top Hats and Champagne's total defeat are greatly exaggerated.
				There are rumors swirling that Top Hats and Champagne has been practicing relentlessly and may face off against Project Dugachug in the near future.
				As many of you saw in the last episode of Top Hats Exposed, Hobo was taken prisoner after the space battle against General The Destroyer.
				PartTim3Hobo was thrown into Top Hats and Champagne's basement and locked down there.
				But Hobo was not alone.
				For many years a failed science experiment was trapped down there.
				Top Hats and Champagne had tried to fuse his DNA with potatoes in an attempt to grow more clones of himself.
				However things went horribly wrong when the potato began conducting the electricity being sent through the cloning machine.
				His name was Potato Pole.
				He told Hobo of the suffering Top Hats and Champagne put him through.
				Many of you are aware that Top Hats and Champagne drinks large amounts of alcohol on stream.
				But what you may not be aware of is the fact that Potato Pole is the one brewing all of this alcohol himself.
				He's forced to betray his one true family, the potatoes, and turn them into potato vodka for Top Hats and Champagne's enjoyment.
				Top Hats and Champagne often lies about this on stream by saying he buys all of his vodka.
				He even emotionally abuses Potato Pole to the point where he is incapable of expressing any emotion anymore.
				The potatoes that Top Hats and Champagne forces his subscribers to mine in the concentration camps are all descendents of Potato Pole.
				Hobo knew then what he had to do.
				Hobo had to start a GoFundMe account for Potato Pole and beg for donations to set him free.
				"For just $10 a month you can help rescue a concentraion camp victim.
				Your money will go towards paying for Navy SEALS to rescue Potato Pole.
				You'll recieve weekly updates on how many potatoes were harvested by Potato Pole that week.
				And if you ever stop paying your subscription Hobo will personally make sure you end up in the same concentration camp as Potato Pole."
				Hobo knew he had to set Potato Pole free so he could avenge his family.
				Potato Pole and PartTim3Hobo used the GPS tracking software in Top Hats and Champagne's spaceship to locate where he was going to land.
				He landed on a small island called Erangel.
				After learning of this Potato Pole and Hobo had to figure out a way to escape the basement.
				We basically just walked through the front door because Top Hats and Champagne was too drunk to remember to lock it.
				From there they hopped on a military cargo plane and took off for Erangel.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_PTH_THAC_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>-</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_PTH_THAC_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>-</Text>
		</Row>
		
		
		<!--Diplomacy-->
		<!--FIRST MEET-->
		<!--First AI line-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cheers sir or madam, I can't really tell. I'm really drunk. Would you like a glass of champagne?</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--AI invitation to visit nearby City-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_VISIT_RECIPIENT_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Do you want to come and visit my city? It has cocaine parties all the time.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--AI accepts Human invitation-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NEAR_INITIATOR_POSITIVE_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Let me come and inspect your city, I bet it's not as efficient as mine.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--AI invitation to exchange Capital Information-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NO_MANS_INFO_EXCHANGE_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Let's compare Cities, I know that yours will be trash, but you can look at mine for help!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--GREETINGS-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_GREETING_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You alright mate?</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--DELEGATION-->
		<!--AI Accepts-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Thanks for the delegation. We'll be sure to get them as drunk as possible before sending them home.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--AI Rejects-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ha, I don't want your delegation they're probably weebs anyway.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--AI Requests -->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DELEGATION_FROM_AI_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I have sent you a delegation with champagne and cocaine!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--OPEN BORDERS-->
		<!--AI accepts from human-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Boy you really are as gullible as Merkel. Don't you know open borders never works.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--AI rejects from human-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>What are you, some kind of American that likes walls instead? </Text>
		</Row>
		<!--AI requests from human-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_OPEN_BORDERS_FROM_AI_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Open your borders... For reasons... Many of which involve cocaine...</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--DECLARE FRIENDSHIP-->
		<!--AI accepts from human-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Yeah alright, we can be friends... For now...</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--AI Rejects from human -->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ha I don't want to be friends with you... Fucking console peasant...</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--AI Requests friendship from human-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hey, do you want to be friends? We can team up and wreck those other weebs!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Human accepts AI requests, AI responds-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>My Man!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Human rejects AI requests, AI responds-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_DECLARE_FRIEND_FROM_AI_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>That's fine, it means I can just feed you to Potato Pole instead...</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--ALLIANCE-->
		<!--AI Requests an alliance from human-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_ALLIANCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Join forces with me, and together we will drink all the vodka and snort all the cocaine!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--KUDOS & WARNINGS-->
		<!--AI Kudos-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_KUDO_EXIT_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Odin smiles upon you.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--AI Warnings-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_EXIT_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Stop Chrissplaining to me REEEEEEEEEEE!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--AI warns player for border troops-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_WARNING_TOO_MANY_TROOPS_NEAR_ME_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I see those troops on my borders... And I will farm them for XP if your not careful!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--TRADE-->
		<!--AI Accepts Deal-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>This will go nicely with my alcohol collection.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--AI Rejects Deal-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_REJECT_MAKE_DEAL_FROM_AI_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I reject your deal because I don't just want your men. I want your women and children too.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--DENOUNCE-->
		<!--From Human-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>HAHA! Do you know what? Good... Go ahead and shoot at me in 5 turns... I dare you!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--From AI-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DENOUNCE_FROM_AI_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Watching you play this game is like watching a Japanese car crash in slow motion. You are inefficient, bad and just a massive weeb. Go learn how to play Civilization from a real Civilization game like CIV 4 you complete twat. (Denounces You)</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--DECLARE WAR-->
		<!--Human Declares War-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>OH HELL YEAH! Now we are talking... I have vodka powered nukes by the way...</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--AI Declares War-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DECLARE_WAR_FROM_AI_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>You have broken rules 1 and 2 too many times! Time to get a swift banhammer to your skull you absolute pest!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--MAKE PEACE-->
		<!--AI accepts from human-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_ACCEPT_DEAL_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Meh, I was bored anyway... Back to the cocaine snorting and fun times with other men.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--AI refuses human-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_AI_REFUSE_DEAL_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Did you really just try to offer peace with me? You must be as weak as Console Fairy.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--AI requests from human-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_MAKE_PEACE_FROM_AI_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Right, I need to go feed Potato Pole in the basement so let's make peace then carry this on later...</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--DEFEAT-->
		<!--AI is Defeated-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DEFEAT_FROM_AI_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>I did not click that! Time to save scum! I bet you're playing on settler difficulty! Screw it, I'm going to Valhalla!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Human is Defeated (will see this in hotseat)-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_DIPLO_DEFEAT_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ANY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Now just imagine Hollow reaching back with a grenade yelling "Allahu Akbar" and blowing up your capital city. That's what this victory feels like.</Text>
		</Row>




		
		
		
		
		
		

		<!--Traits-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ECO_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Top Hat Hoarder</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_TRAIT_LEADER_PTH_THAC_ECO_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+1 Extra Economic Slot in any government.</Text>
		</Row>


		<Row Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_PTH_GRIND_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Viking Blood Line</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_TRAIT_CIVILIZATION_PTH_GRIND_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+75% Experience for all units. When killing a unit, you recieve [Icon_Gold] Gold equal to it's Combat Strength.</Text>
		</Row>



		<Row Tag="LOC_BUILDING_PTH_CUSTOM_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Viking Top Hat Bar</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_BUILDING_PTH_CUSTOM_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+5 [Icon_Strength] Combat Strength Vs Barbarians for each Viking Top Hat Bar built.</Text>
		</Row>


		













	</LocalizedText>
</GameData>
